MUHAMMAD ANAS AFZAAL

B-185 Saghir Centre, Block-16 F.B Area, Karachi.

Phone: +(92)312 3616359 Email: anaskhan.all95@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer - Aimviz (March 2022 - Present)

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of Web Applications.

Technologies & Skills: Angular, JavaScript, TypeScript, ASP.NET, MSSQL, C#, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap.

Front end Developer – Symits (September 2020 – February 2022)

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of WordPress and custom websites.

Technologies & Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, jQuery, WordPress, Shopify and, Adobe Photoshop.

Front end Developer – Optimal Creations (March 2020 – August 2020)

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of WordPress and custom websites and content writing for websites and social media marketing.

Technologies & Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, jQuery, WordPress, Shopify.

EDUCATION

- ➤ Masters of Computer Science (MCS) University of Karachi (February 2021— Present)
- ➤ Bachelors of Computer Science (BCS) University of Karachi (February 2016 December 2018)
- ➤ Intermediate (Pre-Engineering) D.J Science College (February 2016 — December 2018)
- Matriculation (Computer Science) Metropolitan Academy (April 1999 – February 2012)

SUMMARY

I am a Frontend Developer who understands and manages the user interface according to the users' needs and the best of the experience.

I have core expertise in the latest technologies and trends such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, Angular, React, C#, SQL name a few.

LINKS

Portfolio

<u>LinkedIn:</u>

SKILLS

| avaScript: | |
|-------------|--|
| Angular: | |
| ГуреScript: | |
| Query: | |
| C#: | |
| SQL: | |
| Git: | |
| HTML: | |
| CSS: | |
| SCSS: | |
| ASP.NET: | |
| VordPress: | |
| Poact. | |